Guide to the Farmers Market Nutrition Program records, 1988-2003.
Farmers Market Nutrition Program records, 1988-2003
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Farmers Market Nutrition Program records, 1988-2003.
29-4-3429
Cornell Cooperative Extension.Farmers Market Nutrition Program.
1.3 cubic ft.
Reports, Publications, Correspondence
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Includes reports, publications, correspondence, proposals, and questionnaires concerning farmers' markets, the Expanded Food and Nutrition Education Program (EFNEP) and the Special Supplemental Nutrition Program for Women, Infants and Children (WIC).
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Includes reports, publications, correspondence, proposals, and questionnaires concerning farmers' markets, the Expanded Food and Nutrition Education Program (EFNEP) and the Special Supplemental Nutrition Program for Women, Infants and Children (WIC).
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell Cooperative Extension.; Expanded Food and Nutrition Education Program (U.S.); Special Supplemental Food Program for Women, Infants and Children (U.S.); Special Supplemental Nutrition Program for Women, Infants and Children (U.S.)
Subjects:
Farmers' markets--United States.; Produce trade--United States.; Food relief--Law and legislation--United States.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Final Report; General info, Correspondence, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Proposal; Evaluation; Annual Project Operations Report, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Program results; Field study; Memorandum of Understanding; Managers survey; Farmer's survey and comments, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Correspondence, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- General information; Collaboration; Resources; Survey of data; For counties without EFNEP, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Annual Project Operations Report, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Correspondence; Program Report; Evaluation; General Ag and Markets information, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Project Operations Report; Resources; Farmer survey and comments; Close-out report; WIC sites, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Correspondence; Collaboration; Resources; Program Report, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Memorandum of Understanding; Evaluation; State Report; CCE Summary; Highlights; Evaluation of Coupon Demos, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Project Operations Report and 1992 Plan for Program Operations, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- CCE Annual Report; Ag and Markets Surveys; Redemptions; Correspondence; Order Forms, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Communication; WIC Report; CCE Report; New York State Report; Evaluation Forms; Reports turned in (by County), 1993 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Order for Materials; Resources, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Communication; CCE Report; Memorandum of Understanding; New York State Annual Report; WIC Report, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Participating Organizations; Farmer Benefits, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Farmer Benefits; New York State Annual Report; CCE Program Report; WIC Report; Memorandum of Understanding, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Communication; Program Impact Report; Order Forms; Food Safety, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Nutrition Awareness/Education Component; Participant contact information; Questionnaire related to resources; Report information; General information, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Evaluation forms; Communication; Order forms, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Memorandum of Understanding; New York State Report; CCE Report; Ag and Markets Surveys, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Directory of Participating Organizations; WIC program activity; CCE contacts by county, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Participant Questionnaire, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Participating Counties and markets; Order forms and receipts, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- General information; Memorandum of Understanding; CCE Report; New York City Report; Communication, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Program Report Originals: Directory of Participating Organizations, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Farmer/Vendor Questionnaire, by county, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- EFNEP Participant Questionnaire, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- EFNEP Participant Questionnaire, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- County Program Reports, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Participation Questionnaire, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Correspondence, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Program Reports, by County (Albany-Genesee), 1998 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Program Reports, by County (Greene-Oswego), 1998 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Program Reports, by County (Otsego-Wyoming), 1998 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Directory of participating organizations, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Education and Awareness Forms; Evaluation Packet; Correspondence; Participating markets, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Summary Report; CCE Annual Report; Pilot Program; Educational Materials, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Participant Commitment Forms; Educational Resources Request; CCE Draft, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Annual Report, Program Impact Report, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Annual Report, Program Impact Report, Program Summary, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Annual Report, Program Impact Report, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Annual Report, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Correspondence, Memos, Programs, Reports, 1997-1999 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Correspondence, Memos, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Correspondence, Memos, Reports, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Correspondence, Memos, Programs, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Directory of Participating Organizations, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Workshop "A Cornucopia of Collaboration", 2001 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- "Get Fresh" Toolkit and Conference Packet, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Toolkit and Source Book, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Video Series Information, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- National Association of Farmer's Market Nutrition Programs, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 14)